Contact

ankitgarg11@hotmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ankit-garg-9434b8138 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Java

PHP

R

Languages

Spanish (Elementary)

German (Elementary)

Hindi (Limited Working)

Certifications

Spring: Spring MVC

Persuading Others

Python - Introduction to NumPy for Multi-dimensional Data

Python - Manipulating & Analyzing Data in Pandas DataFrames

Python for Data Science: Basic Data Visualization Using Seaborn

Ankit Garg

Software Engineer at Accenture

Gurgaon

Summary

Experienced Software Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in Python , Data Science, Java ,Spring MVC,Hibernate, C .Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor of Technology - BTech focused in Computer Software Engineering from The NorthCap University.

Experience

Accenture
Application Developer
November 2019 - Present (10 months)
Gurgaon, India

MAGES Studio
Emerging Tech(VR/AR) Intern
June 2018 - July 2018 (2 months)

Encriss Technologies Requirements Analysis Intern May 2017 - July 2017 (3 months) Gurgaon, Haryana, India

Education

The NorthCap University
Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Computer Science

Sanatan Dharam Vidya Mandir 12th, Science · (2014)

Sanatan Dharam Vidya Mandir 10th